Adrià Mitjavila Ventura

Bioinformatician

☆ Girona (Spain) - Milan (Italy) adria.mitjavila94@gmail.com
amitjavilaventura.github.io amitjavilaventura

Biotechnologist living around computers, pursuing a PhD in Computational Biology and interested in data analysis to support experimental research as well as in pure computational experiments and in software/pipeline development.

Education _____

Scuola Europea di Medicina Molecolare, PhD. Computational Biology	2019 - Present
Universitat Oberta de Catalunya, MSc. Bioinformatics and Biostatistics	2018 - Present
Universidad de Sevilla, MSc. Molecular Genetics and Biotechnology	2017 - 2018
Universitat de Girona, BSC. Biotechnology	2012 - 2017

Employment ____

Milan (Italy)	Istituto Europeo di Oncologia
10/2019 - Present	PhD Candidate in Computational Biology
07/2019 - 10/2019	Bioinformatician
Seville (Spain)	Instituto de Biomedicina de Sevilla
07/2018 - 10/2018	Research assistant
09/2017 - 07/2018	Master's thesis student
Girona (Spain)	Institut d'Investigació Biomèdica de Girona
07/2017 - 09/2017	Research internship student
Girona (Spain)	Microbial. Sistemes i aplicacions analítiques, S.L.
01/2017 - 06/2017	Bachelor's thesis student
09/2016 - 06/2017	Internship student

Publications _____

JOURNAL ARTICLES

Begley et al. 2020 Xrn1 influence on gene transcription results from the combination of general effects on elongating RNA pol II and gene-specific chromatin configuration. RNA Biology. DOI: 10.1080/15476286.2020.1845504.

References __

Available upon request.

Updated: Mar. 22, 2021 1/1